Ravikant Gupta sir has a buying of Rs 850 in Aditya Birla AMC Slife AMC,
today it is
below.  What should be done?
See, today it is down because
a news came regarding the charges etc. of mutual funds.
I think these are just short term
corrections.  Ah, all the AMC
stocks are still current because at that time,
Sir, we also saw with BSE, like the
news regarding derivatives had come out and
after the statement given by SEBI Chairman Pandey ji, we saw that
selling pressure was being seen in all such counters like BSE, CDSL, NSDL, Njl One,
after that they bounced back and
sustained it and now the
news that has come regarding AMC companies is that because their
maximum revenue comes
from their expense ratio.  So
somewhere temporary is a feedback.  But
if I talk about transparency,
I think from the investors'
perspective, it is going to become
even more transparent over the long term.
And people have still not invested in India.  There
is such a huge EVM and EVM is increasing over the years.
So this is again similar to what happened
with BSE and CDSL stock.
I think the same thing is going to happen with AMC stock.
You will see some
corrections in a day or three.
But in every dip
you should think about accumulation.
And in a particular stock, I feel
that once it breaks out of the current zone, a correction of 5 to 7% is yet to come.
You should go deep on that correction by buying it.
Ok.